Inventaris van het Archief van de Raad voor de Scheepvaart (1908) 1909-2010
Nationaal Archief, Den Haag
- Bijzonder, B.
  - Taakuitvoering, B.2
    - Onderzoek scheepsongevallen, B.2.7
      - Scheepsdossiers, B.2.7.2
        - Dossiers betreffende onderzoeken van de Raad voor de Scheepvaart naar aanleiding van ongevallen en klachten, met uitspraken en beschikkingen van de raad., 1909-2010; 1-442, 571-2171; 2029 pakken en 14 omslagen
          - 14086-14087, 1795; pak
          - 14088-14089, 1796; pak
          - 14090-14095, 1797; pak
          - 14096-14100, 1798; pak
          - 14101-14105, 1799; pak
          - 14106-14111, 1800; pak
          - 14112-14114, 1801; pak
          - 14115-14120, 1802; pak
          - 14121-14125, 1803; pak
          - 14126-14129, 1804; pak
          - 14129, 1805; pak
          - 14130-14131, 1806; pak
          - 14132-14136, 1807; pak
          - 14137-14139, 1808; pak
          - 14140, 1809; pak
          - 14141-14149, 1810; pak
          - 14149-14150, 1811; pak
          - 14151-14155, 1812; pak
          - 14156-14158, 1813; omslag
          - 14159-14162, 1814; pak
          - 14163, 1815; pak
          - 14163, 1816; pak
          - 14164, 1817; pak
          - 14164, 1818; pak
          - 14164, 1819; pak
          - 14164, 1820; pak
          - 14165-14169, 1821; pak
          - 14170-14173, 1822; pak
          - 14174-14179, 1823; pak
          - 14180-14183, 1824; pak
          - 14184-14190, 1825; pak
          - 14191-14194, 1826; pak
          - 14195-14202, 1827; pak
          - 14203-14207, 1828; pak
          - 14208-14213, 1829; pak
          - 14214-14219, 1830; pak
          - 14220, 1831; pak
          - 14220, 1832; pak
          - 14220, 1833; pak
          - 14220, 1834; pak
          - 14220, 1835; pak
          - 14220, 1836; pak
          - 14220, 1837; pak
          - 14221-14225, 1838; pak
          - 14226-14228, 1839; pak
          - 14229-14230, 1840; pak
          - 14231-14238, 1841; pak
          - 14239, 1842; pak
          - 14240-14242, 1843; pak
          - 14243-14248, 1844; pak
          - 14249, 1845; omslag
          - 14250-14259, 1846; pak
          - 14260-14264, 1847; pak
          - 14265-14275, 1848; pak
          - 14276-14279, 1849; pak
          - 14281-14284, 1850; pak
          - 14285-14288, 1851; pak
          - 14289-14293, 1852; pak
          - 14294-14296, 1853; pak
          - 14298-14301, 1854; pak
          - 14302-14308, 1855; pak
          - 14309-14314, 1856; pak
          - 14315-14318, 1857; pak
          - 14319-14321, 1858; pak
          - 14322-14325, 1859; pak
          - 14326-14329, 1860; pak
          - 14330-14337, 1861; pak
          - 14338-14342, 1862; pak
          - 14343-14347, 1863; pak
          - 14348, 1864; pak
          - 14349-14353, 1865; pak
          - 14354-14358, 1866; pak
          - 14359-14362, 1867; pak
          - 14363-14368, 1868; pak
          - 14369-14376, 1869; pak
          - 14377-14383, 1870; pak
          - 14384-14388, 1871; pak
          - 14389-14396, 1872; pak
          - 14397-14401, 1873; pak
          - 14402-14405, 1874; pak
          - 14406-14410, 1875; pak
          - 14411-14414, 1876; pak
          - 14415-14417, 1877; pak
          - 14418-14423, 1878; pak
          - 14424-14429, 1879; pak
          - 14429, 1880; pak
          - 14430, 1881; omslag
          - 14431-14434, 1882; pak
          - 14435-14443, 1883; pak
          - 14444-14446, 1884; pak
          - 14447, 1885; pak
          - 14448, 1886; pak
          - 14449, 1887; pak
          - 14450, 1888; pak
          - 14450, 1889; pak
          - 14452-14455, 1890; pak
          - 14456-14457, 1891; pak
          - 14458-14459, 1892; pak
          - 14460-14462, 1893; pak
          - 14463-14464, 1894; pak
          - 14465-14470, 1895; pak
          - 14471, 1896; pak
          - 14472, 1897; pak
          - 14473-14477, 1898; pak
          - 14478-14482, 1899; pak
          - 14483-14485, 1900; pak
          - 14486-14491, 1901; pak
          - 14492-14497, 1902; pak
          - 14498-14500, 1903; pak
          - 14501-14503, 1904; pak
          - 14504-14511, 1905; pak
          - 14512-14516, 1906; pak
          - 14517-14526, 1907; pak
          - 14527-14529, 1908; pak
          - 14530-14533, 1909; pak
          - 14534-14538, 1910; pak
          - 14539-14541, 1911; pak
          - 14542-14546, 1912; pak
          - 14547-14554, 1913; pak
          - 14555-14562, 1914; pak
          - 14563-14566, 1915; pak
          - 14568-14570, 1916; pak
          - 14571-14577, 1917; pak
          - 14578-14580, 1918; pak
          - 14581-14582, 1919; pak
          - 14583-14587, 1920; pak
          - 14588-14589, 1921; pak
          - 14590-14596, 1922; pak
          - 14597-14600, 1923; pak
          - 14601, 1924; pak
          - 14602-14606, 1925; pak
          - 14609, 1926; pak
          - 14610-14615, 1927; pak
          - 14616-14619, 1928; pak
          - 14620-14621, 1929; pak
          - 14622-14626, 1930; pak
          - 14627-14632, 1931; pak
          - 14633, 1932; pak
          - 14634-14636, 1933; pak
          - 14637-14639, 1934; pak
          - 14640, 1935; pak
          - 14641-14643, 1936; pak
          - 14644, 1937; pak
          - 14645, 1938; pak
          - 14645, 1939; pak
          - 14645, 1940; pak
          - 14645, 1941; pak
          - 14646-14648, 1942; pak
          - 14649-14652, 1943; pak
          - 14653-14654, 1944; omslag
          - 14655, 1945; pak
          - 14656, 1946; pak
          - 14657-14662, 1947; pak
          - 14664-14669, 1948; pak
          - 14670-14674, 1949; pak
          - 14675-14677, 1950; pak
          - 14678-14684, 1951; pak
          - 14685-14686, 1952; pak
          - 14687-14694, 1953; pak
          - 14695-14700, 1954; pak
          - 14701, 1955; pak
          - 14702-14710, 1956; pak
          - 14711-14721, 1957; pak
          - 14722-14726, 1958; pak
          - 14727, 1959; pak
          - 14728-14730, 1960; pak
          - 14731-14737, 1961; pak
          - 14738-14739, 1962; omslag
          - 14740, 1963; pak
          - 14741-14745, 1964; pak
          - 14746-14749, 1965; pak
          - 14750-14752, 1966; pak
          - 14753-14756, 1967; pak
          - 14757-14758, 1968; pak
          - 14759-14763, 1969; pak
          - 14764-14769, 1970; pak
          - 14770, 1971; pak
          - 14771-14773, 1972; pak
          - 14774-14777, 1973; pak
          - 14778-14781, 1974; pak
          - 14782-14787, 1975; pak
          - 14788-14792, 1976; pak
          - 14793-14796, 1977; pak
          - 14797-14804, 1978; pak
          - 14805-14807, 1979; pak
          - 14808-14810, 1980; pak
          - 14811-14815, 1981; pak
          - 14816-14817, 1982; pak
          - 14818-14820, 1983; pak
          - 14821-14822, 1984; pak
          - 14823-14824, 1985; pak
          - 14824-14826, 1986; pak
          - 14827-14829, 1987; pak
          - 14830-14832, 1988; pak
          - 14833-14834, 1989; pak
          - 14835, 1990; pak
          - 14835-14839, 1991; pak
          - 14840-14843, 1992; pak
          - 14845-14849, 1993; pak
          - 14850, 1994; omslag
          - 14851, 1995; pak
          - 14851, 1996; pak
          - 14851, 1997; pak
          - 14851, 1998; pak
          - 14852, 1999; pak
          - 14853-14854, 2000; pak
          - 14855-14861, 2001; pak
          - 14862-14865, 2002; pak
          - 14866, 2003; pak
          - 14866, 2004; pak
          - 14866, 2005; pak
          - 14866-14867, 2006; pak
          - 14868-14869, 2007; pak
          - 14870-14872, 2008; pak
          - 14873-14875, 2009; pak
          - 14876-14878, 2010; pak
          - 14879-14883, 2011; pak
          - 14884-14886, 2012; pak
          - 14887-14891, 2013; pak
          - 14892-14895, 2014; pak
          - 14896-14897, 2015; pak
          - 14898-14900, 2016; pak
          - 14901-14905, 2017; pak
          - 14906-14909, 2018; pak
          - 14910-14911, 2019; pak
          - 14912, 2020; pak
          - 14913-14916, 2021; pak
          - 14917-14920, 2022; pak
          - 14921-14925, 2023; pak
          - 14926-14929, 2024; pak
          - 14930-14932, 2025; pak
          - 14933-14936, 2026; pak
          - 14937-14938, 2027; pak
          - 14939, 2028; pak
          - 14939, 2029; pak
          - 14939-14941, 2030; pak
          - 14942-14948, 2031; pak
          - 14949-14950, 2032; pak
          - 14950, 2033; pak
          - 14951-14953, 2034; pak
          - 14954-14957, 2035; pak
          - 14958-14965, 2036; pak
          - 14966-14968, 2037; pak
          - 14969-14972, 2038; pak
          - 14973-14975, 2039; pak
          - 14976-14979, 2040; pak
          - 14980, 14982, 2041; pak
          - 14983, 2042; pak
          - 14984-14985, 2043; omslag
          - 14986, 2044; pak
          - 14987-14988, 2045; omslag
          - 14989-14990, 2046; pak
          - 14991-14995, 2047; pak
          - 14996, 2048; pak
          - 14997, 2049; pak
          - 14998, 2050; pak
          - 14999-15001, 2051; pak
          - 15002, 2052; pak
          - 15003-15004, 2053; pak
          - 15005-15010, 2054; pak
          - 15011, 2055; pak
          - 15012, 2056; pak
          - 15013-15017, 2057; pak
          - 15018-15020, 2058; pak
          - 15021-15022, 2059; pak
          - 15024-15031, 2060; pak
          - 15032-15036, 2061; pak
          - 15037-15038, 2062; pak
          - 15039-15040, 2063; pak
          - 15041, 2064; pak
          - 15042-15044, 2065; omslag
          - 15045-15046, 2066; pak
          - 15047-15048, 2067; pak
          - 15049, 2068; pak
          - 15049, 2069; pak
          - 15050-15051, 2070; pak
          - 15052-15053, 2071; pak
          - 15054-15060, 2072; pak
          - 15061-15063, 2073; pak
          - 15064, 2074; pak
          - 15065, 2075; pak
          - 15066-15068, 2076; pak
          - 15069-15070, 2077; pak
          - 15071-15072, 2078; pak
          - 15073-15074, 2079; pak
          - 15075-15076, 2080; pak
          - 15077-15080, 2081; pak
          - 15081, 15084-15086, 2082; pak
            Nota bene: dossiers 15082 en 15083 ontbreken
          - 15087, 15089-15095, 2083; pak
            Nota bene: dossier 15088 ontbreekt
          - 15096-15098, 2084; pak
          - 15099-15103, 2085; pak
          - 15104-15105, 2086; pak
          - 15106-15107, 2087; pak
          - 15108-15112, 2088; pak
          - 15113-15117, 2089; pak
          - 15118-15119, 2090; pak
          - 15120-15121, 2091; pak
          - 15122-15127, 2092; pak
          - 15128-15131, 2093; pak
          - 15132-15135, 2094; pak
          - 15136-15141, 2095; pak
          - 15142-15143, 2096; pak
          - 15144-15145, 2097; pak
          - 15146-15147, 2098; pak
          - 15148, 2099; pak
          - 15149-15150, 2100; pak
          - 15151-15154, 2101; pak
          - 15155, 2102; pak
          - 15156-15160, 2103; pak
          - 15161-15162, 2104; pak
          - 15163-15169, 2105; pak
          - 15170, 2106; pak
          - 15171-15173, 2107; pak
          - 15173-15179, 2108; pak
          - 15180-15184, 2109; pak
          - 15186-15190, 2110; pak
          - 15191-15195, 2111; pak
          - 15196-15198, 2112; pak
          - 15199, 2113; pak
          - 15199, 2114; pak
          - 15200-15203, 2115; pak
          - 15204-15209; 15211, 2116; pak
            Nota bene: dossier 15210 ontbreekt
          - 15212-15219, 2117; pak
          - 15220-15223, 2118; pak
          - 15224-15236, 2119; pak
          - 15237-15242, 2120; pak
          - 15243-15249, 2121; pak
          - 15250-15256, 2122; pak
          - 15257-15263, 2123; pak
          - 15263, 2124; pak
          - 15263, 2125; pak
          - 15263-15264, 2126; pak
          - 15265; 15267-15269, 2127; pak
            Nota bene: dossier 15266 ontbreekt
          - 15273-15279, 2128; pak
          - 15271, 2129; pak
          - 15272, 2130; pak
          - 15272, 2131; pak
          - 15272, 2132; pak
          - 15272, 2133; pak
          - 15273-15279, 2134; pak
          - 15280-15285, 2135; pak
          - 15286-15289, 2136; pak
          - 15290-15296, 2137; pak
          - 15297-15305, 2138; pak
          - 15306-15312, 2139; pak
          - 15313-15316, 2140; pak
          - 15317-15321, 2141; pak
          - 15322-15324, 2142; pak
          - 15325-15327, 2143; pak
          - 15328-15330, 2144; pak
          - 15331-15337, 2145; pak
          - 15338-15343, 2146; pak
          - 15344-15347, 2147; pak
          - 15348-15353, 2148; pak
          - 15354, 2149; pak
          - 15355-15358, 2150; pak
          - 15359, 2151; pak
          - 15360-15365, 2152; pak
          - 15366-15372, 2153; pak
          - 15373; 15375-15377, 2154; pak
            Nota bene: dossier 15374 ontbreekt
          - 15378-15380, 2155; pak
          - 15381-15387, 2156; pak
          - 15388-15396, 2157; pak
          - 15397-15398, 2158; pak
          - 15400-15403, 2159; pak
          - 15404, 2160; pak
          - 15405-15410, 2161; pak
          - 15411-15413, 2162; pak
          - 15414-15418, 2163; pak
          - 15419-15424, 2164; pak
          - 15425-15427, 2165; pak
          - 15428-15430, 2166; pak
          - 15431-15435, 2167; pak
          - 15436-15438, 2168; pak
          - 15439-15440, 2169; pak
          - 15440, 2170; pak
          - 15441-15443, 2171; pak
        - Beschikkingen van de Commissie van de Raad voor de Scheepvaart, 2000-2009; 2172; pak
          Het betreft besluiten van de Raad of een onderzoek wel of niet wordt ingesteld.
      - Ter documentatie aangeschafte Zeekaarten, B.2.7.3
        Er bestaat veelal een direct verband tussen de scheepsdossiers en de zeekaarten; op de kaarten staat dan het betreffende dossiernummer vermeld.
        - Corrrespondentie en catalogi, B.2.7.3.1
          - Correspondentie betreffende (zee)kaarten, 1918-1941; 2293; omslag
          - 'Algemene toelichting op de samenstelling en het gebruik van de Nederlandse zeekaarten, zeemansgidsen en verdere uitgaven der afdeling Hydrografie' en 'Toelichting hydrografische publikaties 1962', 1949-1962; 2294; omslag
          - Catalogue of Admiralty Charts and other hydrographic publications, 1967, 1992; 2295-2296; 2 stukken
            Nota bene: Zie ook rubriek B.2.7.3.2 en B.2.7.3.3, de nummering van de zeekaarten komt overeen met de nummering in deze catalogi (niet van toepassing op diverse Nederlandse zeekaarten)
            - 1967, 2295
              kaart
            - 1992, 2296
          - Catalogue of Netherlands sea charts and other hydrographic publications, 1993, 1998; 2297-2298; 2 stukken
            - 1993, 2297
            - 1998, 2298
          - Home Waters Catalogue Admiralty Charts and other Hydrographic Publications, 1988; 2299; stuk
          - Tekens en afkortingen voorkomend op de Nederlandse zeekaarten, december 1982; 2300; stuk
        - British Admiralty Charts, B.2.7.3.2
          - Atlantic Ocean, B.2.7.3.2.1
            - Coastal waters east coast South America, B.2.7.3.2.1.1
              - 504: Pôrto de Natal and approaches, 4th November 1949, 2301; blad
              - 506: Porto do São Salvador, 4th April 1947 (last correction 1948), 2302; blad
              - 521: Porto de Vitória and Porto du Tubarão, 13th May 1988 (last correction 1991), 2303; blad
              - 528: São Luis to Recife, 19th February 1954, 2304; blad
              - 528: São Luís to Recife, 19th February 1954 (revised 1961), 2305; blad
              - 529: Recife to Rio de Janeiro, 24th February 1956 (revised 1961), 2306; blad
              - 530: Brazil east coast (sheet II) - Vitória to Santa Catarina, 30th April 1833 (revised 1961), 2307; blad
              - 541: Rio de Janeiro and approaches, 24th August 1945 (revised 1962), 2308; blad
              - 546: Porto da Victoria and Bahia do Espirito Santo, 31st December 1929 (last correction 1930), 2309; blad
              - 546: Pôrto do Salvador, Pôrto do Ilhéus, Baia Cabrália and Pôrto do Vitória, 23rd August 1957 (revised 1962), 2310; blad
              - 550: Porto de São Francisca do Sul, 10th September 1943 (last correction 1947), 2311; blad
              - 969: Porto de Recife, 28th February 1887 (last correction 1949), 2312; blad
              - 1302: Cabo Guardian to Punta Nava, 6th March 1917 (revised 1963) (last correction 1984), 2313; blad
              - 1309: Puerto Deseado - Bahia Oso Marino, 15th July 1899 (last correction 1946), 2314; blad
              - 1324: Rio de la Plata to Cabo dos Bahias, 31st January 1902 (revised 1960), 2315; blad
              - 1331: Approaches to Bahia Blanca and Puerto Belgrano, 16th April 1937 (last correction 1947), 2316; blad
              - 1336: Cape Virgins to First Narrows - east entrance of Magellan Strait, 1st April 1869 (last correction 1973), 2317; blad
              - 1337: First Narrows to Punta Arenosa, 1st April 1869 (last correction 1974), 2318; blad
              - 1396: Rio Paraiba entrance - Porto de Aracajú, 16th March 1932 (last correction 1949), 2319; blad
              - 1749: Rio de la Plata - Montevideo to Buenos Aires, 29th October 1937 (revised 1966) (last correction 1972), 2320; blad
              - 1751: Puerto de Buenos Aires - Puerto de la Plata, 8th July 1955 (last correction 1970), 2321; blad
              - 1802: Suriname Rivier to Cabo do Norte, 26th April 1852 (revised 1961), 2322; blad
              - 1803: Cabo do Norte to São Luis, 26th April 1852 (revised 1961), 2323; blad
              - 2186: Rio Pará, 7th July 1853 (revised 1963), 2324; blad
              - 2189: Approaches to Macapá and Porto de Santana, 30th September 1960 (last correction 1969), 2325; blad
              - 2190: Rio Amazonas, Barra Norte, 12th May 1961 (last correction 1968), 2326; blad
              - 2204: Rio Amazonas, Macapá en Belém to Almeirim, 14th December 1962 (last correction 1966), 2327; blad
              - 2229: Rio Amazonas, Almeirim to Manaus, 14th December 1962 (revised 1969) (last correction 1971), 2328; blad
              - 2522: I. de Sta. Catarina to Rio de la Plata, 4th April 1866 (revised 1961), 2329; blad
              - 3064: Rio de la Plata, Punta Coronilla to Cabo San Antonio, 26th May 1939 (last correction 1954), 2330; blad
              - 3064: Rio de la Plata, Punta Coronilla to Cabo San Antonio, 26th May 1939 (last correction 1972), 2331; blad
              - 3065: Punta Piedras to Quequen, 4th June 1943 (last correction 1959), 2332; blad
              - 3066: Quequen to Rio Negro, 17th March 1939 (last correction 1947), 2333; blad
              - 3106: Isla Leones to Pte. San Julian, 12th October 1956 (revised 1959) (last correction 1984), 2334; blad
              - 3107: Cape St. Thomé to Guaratiba Point including the approaches to Rio de Janeiro, 12th August 1899 (last correction 1937), 2335; blad
              - 3108: Rio Doce to Cape St. Thomé, 9th February 1900 (last correction 1934), 2336; blad
              - 3226: Puertos Santa Cruz and San Julian, 24th December 1953, 2337; blad
              - 3561: Rio de la Plata - Buenos Aires to Nueva Palmira, 13th October 1933 (last correction 1956), 2338; blad
              - 3561: Rio de la Plata - Buenos Aires and Colonia to Nueva Palmira, 13th October 1933 (revised 1965) (last correction 1972), 2339; blad
              - 3610: Magellan Strait - Willes, Harriss and Fox Bays, 19th November 1906 (last correction 1943), 2340; blad
              - 3755: Bahia Blanca - inner port, 19th July 1910 (last correction 1946), 2341; blad
              - 3755: Bahia Blanca, 27th November 1981 (revised 1991) (last correction 1992), 2342; blad
              - 3970: Rio de Janeiro to Ilha de São Sebastião, 28th December 1951 (revised 1961), 2343; blad
              - 3971: Cabo de São Tomé to Rio de Janeiro, 28th December 1951 (last correction 1952), 2344; blad
            - Coastal waters east coast USA, Canada and Central America, B.2.7.3.2.1.2
              - 232a: Newfoundland - southern portion, 30th June 1870 (last correction 1971), 2345; blad
              - 232b: Newfoundland - northern portion (last correction 1971), 2346; blad
              - 238: Kilifi River and approaches, 8th April 1891 (last correction 1963), 2347; blad
              - 266: Barnegat Inlet to Chesapeake Bay, 4th April 1923 (last correction 1961), 2348; blad
              - 267: Albemarle Sound to Cape Fear, 19th March 1923 (revised 1959), 2349; blad
              - 280: Notre Dame Bay, 28th July 1881 (last correction 1965), 2350; blad
              - 285: Orange Bay to Gander Bay, 20th February 1883 (last correction 1970), 2351; blad
              - 293: Gander Bay to Cape Bonavista, 31st March 1873 (last correction 1971), 2352; blad
              - 296: Cape Bonavista to Bay Bulls including Trinity and Conception Bays, 10th February 1868 (revised 1968) (last correction 1969), 2353; blad
              - 298: Saint John's Harbour and approaches, 3rd January 1992, 2354; blad
              - 307: Pointe des Monts to Father Point, 14th October 1938 (last correction 1958), 2355; blad
              - 311: Halifax Harbour, 18th February 1955 (revised 1963), 2356; blad
              - 312: Father Point to Green Island, 28th April 1914 (last correction 1958), 2357; blad
              - 313: Saguenay River to Kamouraska Islands, 17th June 1924 (last correction 1958), 2358; blad
              - 314: Kamouraska Islands to Goose Island, 2nd August 1890 (last correction 1957), 2359; blad
              - 315: Goose Island to Quebec, 2nd August 1890 (last correction 1958), 2360; blad
              - 318: North Traverse and South Channel - south-west portion, 5th September 1952 (last correction 1958), 2361; blad
              - 319: Quebec Harbour, 11th March 1955, 2362; blad
              - 332: Great Sound including Hamilton Harbour, 15th May 1941(last correction 1958), 2363; blad
              - 334: Bermuda Islands, 2nd August 1946 (last correction 1957), 2364; blad
              - 334: Bermuda Islands, 2nd August 1946 (last correction 1959), 2365; blad
              - 335: Bermuda Islands - Ireland Island - north and south basins, 14th December 1951 (last correction 1956), 2366; blad
              - 335: Bermuda Islands - Ireland Island - north and south basins, 14th December 1951 (revised 1960), 2367; blad
              - 353: Bay of Fundy - outer sheet, 30th March 1865 (revised 1957) (last correction 1958), 2368; blad
              - 353: Bay of Fundy - sheet 2: Digby Gut to the Head of Navigation, 18th September 1863 (revised 1957) (last correction 1958), 2369; blad
              - 360: Bermuda Islands and off-lying banks, 1st April 1926 (revised 1949), 2370; blad
              - 398: Freeport Harbour and approaches, 9th September 1960, 2371; blad
              - 399: Bahama and Abaco Islands, with the North-West Providence Channel, 30th January 1886 (last correction 1958), 2372; blad
              - 408: Wide opening, Clarence Town Harbour and Mira-por-Vos Passage - harbours and anchorages in the Bahama Islands, 30th December 1897 (revised 1963) (last correction 1988), 2373; blad
              - 421: Montreal Harbour, 12th May 1961 (revised 1967), 2374; blad
              - 422: Quebec to Montreal, 12th August 1960, 2375; blad
              - 423: Montreal to Kingston, 12th August 1960, 2376; blad
              - 525: Boca Grande Key to Dry Tortugas, 1st March 1876 (revised 1950), 2377; blad
              - 527: Approaches to Demerara and Essequibo Rivers, 6th January 1966 (last correction 1971), 2378; blad
              - 533: British Guiana - Georgetown and Mouths of Demerara and Essequibo Rivers, 1st August 1929 (revised 1964), 2379; blad
              - 730: Cape Canso to Sambro Island, 1st October 1867 (last correction 1958), 2380; blad
              - 730: Cape Canso to Sambro Island, 1st October 1867 (revised 1963), 2381; blad